Finding Aid for Office of Financial Aid (University of Michigan) records, 1954-2000 (bulk 1977-1996)
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Alumni Scholarships 1954-2000
  - Prospective Scholars Program 1977-1981 (Box 10)
  - Ralph G. Conger Scholarship 1965-1966, 1991 (Box 10)
  - Recruitment 1984-1985 (Box 10)
  - Regents-Alumni Scholars
    - General 1964-2000 (Box 10)
    - Committee 1972-1974 (Box 11)
    - Proposal for Revising 1974 (Box 11)
  - Robert G. Forman Alumni Fund for Undergraduate Education 1994 (Box 11)
  - Scholar Recruitment and Awards Committee 1981-1986 (Box 11)
  - Schmidhauser Award 1961-1970 (Box 11)
  - Seth Harrison Scholarship 1950-1982 (Box 11)
  - Shipman Scholarships 1994-1997 (Box 11)
  - U-M Clubs
    - General 1960-1994 (Box 11)
    - Scholarship Manual for In-State Clubs 1965 (Box 11)
  - U-M Gay and Lesbian Alumni Society Scholarship Fund 1994 (Box 11)